Erikas Taroza

PROFILE

I am a self-taught software developer with proficiency in Flutter/Dart, Rust, C#, Git, and Linux. When I discovered Flutter, I fell in love with its cross-platform capabilities and have used Flutter in numerous projects. I am an active contributor to open source community, consistently fixing issues, adding new features, or creating my own projects to help other developers. I am confident that my expertise and my passion for creating innovative solutions would add great value to your team.

EXPERIENCE

January 2023 - Present

Full Stack Developer, IDMSRTV (Startup)

- Drive strategy for website development
 - Rewrote WordPress website with improved styling and functionality
 - Vue (front-end)
 - Rust + Docker (back-end)
- Identified and implemented modern technologies to get the beta website to market faster
- Collaborated with cross functional team leaders to define project scope and timelines
- Added ecommerce functionality to order form for customer demo purposes
 - WordPress, PHP
 - Raw JavaScript/HTML/CSS

October 2022 - December 2022

Intern Web Developer, Deidis (Startup)

- Developed widget to provide clients an easy way to capture leads
- · React (front-end)
- · NodeJS (back-end)

ACHIEVEMENTS

Google Cloud Certified

After spending 1 month learning Google Cloud, I am now certified as an Associate Cloud Engineer.

See Certificate

PROJECTS

October 2022 - Present

simple_audio

- · A simple cross-platform solution for playing audio in Flutter
- Rust
- · Open source

May 2022 - Present

BitBeat

- · Music streaming app with no ads
- Flutter (front-end)
- · Rust (back-end)
- Vue (back-end forms)
- Docker

December 2020 - Present

Open Source

Contributing to open source projects by fixing issues, adding new features, or creating my own open source projects.

See my work here: https://github.com/erikas-taroza

EDUCATION

July 2019 - January 2023

Laurel Springs School

High School

- 3.75 GPA (3.90 weighted)
- AP Computer Science (4/5 on AP exam)

July 2016 - Present

Self-Taught

I taught myself everything I know about programming.

SKILLS

Git

- · Critical Thinking
- Computers and Technology
- Research
- Ability to Learn
- · Problem Solving
- Linux